# CRISTINA GORRINO

San Diego, CA 619-322-2314 <u>cgorrino03@gmail.com</u>

Passionate about delivering quality products and representing the voice of the customer. Energized by collaboration across teams to advocate for quality, and by becoming the expert on every facet of the product.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

PRODUCT & COMMUNITY ORGANIZER, GETYOURREFUND.ORG - MARCH 2021-PRESENT

Coordinate volunteer efforts to help achieve the objectives of the Get Your Refund team at Code for America. Responsible for volunteer outreach, onboarding and ongoing communications.

Liaison between staff and volunteers acting as project manager for project requests including information gathering, task assignment, and driving to conclusion

QUALITY ENGINEER, JUNTOS, INC - 2017-PRESENT

As sole QA representative on the engineering team:

Conducted manual tests across array of locales, OS, browsers and devices using BrowserStack tools

Maintained bug backlog and advocated for quality during Agile sprints

Wrote UI tests for client-facing conversation platform and dashboard products

Developed test plans and quality tracking dashboards to share QA efforts company-wide

As QA specialist for the text message conversation product:

Developed SQL queries to monitor message delivery and content accuracy

Designed specialized workflows using JIRA admin tools to clarify review processes for content team and improve customer interactions with conversation product

Created technical documentation used as reference and training material by Operations team

DATA ANALYST, JUNTOS, INC - 2015-2017

Prepared client data for ETL process and maintained data definitions for segmentation analysis

Collaborated with Account Managers to report results of each partnership and analyzed experiment-level data to recommend best path for future conversations to Content team

OPERATIONS SPECIALIST, JUNTOS, INC - 2013-2017

Programmed the logic of interactive SMS conversations using proprietary tools and tested those conversations for accuracy and design compliance. Later trained new team members in this role and became expert on best practices for conversation programming

USER RESEARCH AND CUSTOMER SERVICE, JUNTOS, INC - 2010-2013

Conducted in-person interviews and gathered insights from early users on personal finances leading to tools and conversations more centered on user needs

Processed messages and responded to user questions and comments. Provided insight to management, leading to smoother interactions with customers and better tools for Juntos

### **EDUCATION**

## STANFORD UNIVERSITY – B.A. INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS, 2011

#### **SKILLS**

Experienced in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootrstrap, Node.js, BrowserStack, PostgreSQL, R, Java, Capybara, Minitest, JIRA admin tools, Slack

Fluent in English and Spanish - bilingual native proficiency, French - professional proficiency